A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Peace and Social Justice Program (PSJ), Human Rights and International Cooperation (HRIC), Office Files of Cristina Eguizabal FA613
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grant Files, 1990-2002; 4; 7.89 Cubic Feet 6 record storage boxes
  - Facultad Latinoamericana de Ciencias Sociales (FLACSO) - Chile, Dominican Republic, Costa Rica (Latin American Faculty of Social Sciences) -- GF#980-0340; 980-0281 -- DR (folder 4), 1997-2000 (Box 10)
  - Facultad Latinoamericana de Ciencias Sociales (FLACSO) - Chile, Dominican Republic, Costa Rica (Latin American Faculty of Social Sciences) -- GF#980-0340; 980-0281 -- DR (folder 5), 1998-2000 (Box 10)
  - Facultad Latinoamericana de Ciencias Sociales (FLACSO) - Chile, Dominican Republic, Costa Rica (Latin American Faculty of Social Sciences) -- GF#980-0340; 980-0281 (folder 6), 2000 (Box 10)
  - Facultad Latinoamericana de Ciencias Sociales (FLACSO) - Chile, Dominican Republic, Costa Rica (Latin American Faculty of Social Sciences) -- GF#980-0340; 980-0281 -- Central America -- Report on FLACSO Centers (folder 7), undated (Box 10)
  - Former Members of Congress -- GF#980-1101, 1997-2000 (Box 10)
  - Florida International University -- GF#990-0163; 950-1198 -- Cuban Research Institute (CRI), 1995-1999 (Box 10)
  - Florida International University -- GF#990-0163; 950-1198 (folder 2), 1998-1999 (Box 10)
  - Florida International University -- GF#990-0163; 950-1198 -- Perez-Stable incl. Report Re: Ford Foundation Transitional Justice Meeting, 2000 (Box 10)
  - Fundacion Amistad, Inc. -- GF#10000430-1; 10000430 -- Casa de Las Americas -- Libraries for the Future/Libraries and Archives Initiatives (GF#10000430) (folder 1), 1999-2000 (Box 10)
  - Fundacion Amistad, Inc. -- GF#10000430-1; 10000430 -- Casa de Las Americas (GF#1000430) (folder 2), 1999 (Box 10)
  - Fundacion Amistad, Inc. -- GF#10000430-1; 10000430 -- Progress Report and Proposal (GF#1000430) (folder 3), 2000 (Box 10)
  - Fundacion Amistad, Inc. -- GF#10000430-1; 10000430 (GF#1000430-1) (folder 4), 2000 (Box 10)
  - Fundacion Falconbridge, Inc. -- Arelis Rodriguez -- Correspondence Re: Women's Programs and Note Re: Dominican Republic Photo Book, 1991 (Box 10)
  - Fundacion del Servicio Exterior para la Paz y la Democracia (FUNPADEM/Foundation of Foreign Service for Peace and Democracy), 1996-1997 (Box 10)
  - Fundacion del Servicio Exterior para la Paz y la Democracia (FUNPADEM/Foundation of Foreign Service for Peace and Democracy) -- GF#970-1227, 1998-2000 (Box 10)
  - Georgetown University -- GF#970-0435 -- Caribbean (folder 1), 1993-1996 (Box 11)
  - Georgetown University -- GF#970-0435 -- Caribbean (folder 2), 1996 (Box 11)
  - Georgetown University -- GF#970-0435 -- Washington, DC Meeting (3/24/97) Prep and Related Materials (folder 3), 1997 (Box 11)
  - Georgetown University -- GF#970-0435 -- Meeting with Cristina Eguizabal (folder 4), 1997 (Box 11)
  - Georgetown University -- GF#970-0435 -- Caribbean Project FY 1999-2000 (folder 5), 1997-1998 (Box 11)
  - Georgetown University -- GF#970-0435 -- Caribbean (folder 6), 2002 (Box 11)
  - Hispanics in Philanthropy (HIP) -- GF#990-0161, 1998-2000 (Box 11)
  - Instituto Venezolano de Estudios Sociales y Politicos (INVESP/Venezuelan Institute of Social and Political Studies) -- GF#970-1226 (folder 1), 1994-1996 (Box 11)
  - Instituto Venezolano de Estudios Sociales y Politicos (INVESP/Venezuelan Institute of Social and Political Studies) -- GF#970-1226 (folder 2), 1995-1997 (Box 11)
  - Instituto Venezolano de Estudios Sociales y Politicos (INVESP/Venezuelan Institute of Social and Political Studies) -- GF#970-1226 -- SELA (folder 3), 1996 (Box 11)
  - Instituto Venezolano de Estudios Sociales y Politicos (INVESP/Venezuelan Institute of Social and Political Studies) -- GF#970-1226 (folder 4), 1997 (Box 11)
  - Instituto Venezolano de Estudios Sociales y Politicos (INVESP/Venezuelan Institute of Social and Political Studies) -- GF#970-1226 -- FY 1997-1998 (folder 5) (Box 11)
  - Instituto Venezolano de Estudios Sociales y Politicos (INVESP/Venezuelan Institute of Social and Political Studies) -- GF#970-1226 -- Observatorio (folder 6), 1999 (Box 11)
  - Inter-American Dialogue -- GF#990-1016; 990-1017; 970-0214; 970-02314 (folder 1), 1995-1998 (Box 11)
  - Inter-American Dialogue -- GF#990-1016; 990-1017; 970-0214; 970-02314 (folder 2), 1998-1999 (Box 11)
  - Inter-American Dialogue -- GF#990-1016; 990-1017; 970-0214; 970-02314 -- Colombia (folder 3), 2000 (Box 11)
  - Inter-American Dialogue -- GF#970-0214-1, 1998-2000 (Box 11)
  - International Center for Research on Women -- GF#980-0931 -- Inter-American Dialogue (folder 1), 1993-1995 (Box 11)
  - International Center for Research on Women -- GF#980-0931 -- Inter-American Dialogue (folder 2), 1997-1998 (Box 11)
  - Johns Hopkins University -- GF#970-1334; 960-0527; 830-0827 -- Cuba (folder 1), 1993-1996 (Box 11)
  - Johns Hopkins University -- GF#970-1334; 960-0527; 830-0827 -- $200,000 Cuba Exchange (folder 2), 1996-1997 (Box 11)
  - Latin American Studies Association (LASA) -- GF#980-1092; 855-0401 --Religion -- Cuba (folder 1), 1998 (Box 11)
  - Latin American Studies Association (LASA) -- GF#980-1092; 855-0401 --Religion -- Cuba (folder 2), 1999 (Box 11)
  - Lexington Institute -- GF#10000189, 1999-2002 (Box 11)
  - Miranda Foundation -- GF#10000555, 1999-2001 (Box 11)
  - New School for Social Research/World Policy Institute -- GF#980-0339 (folder 1), 1997 (Box 12)
  - New School for Social Research/World Policy Institute -- GF#980-0339 (folder 2), 1999 (Box 12)
  - New York University -- GF#990-1588; 825-1196, 1997 (Box 12)
  - Oxfam-America, Inc. -- GF#980-1094; 975-0703 -- Food Security in Cuba (folder 1), 1996-1997 (Box 12)
  - Oxfam-America, Inc. -- GF#980-1094; 975-0703 (folder 2), 1998-2000 (Box 12)
  - Pontificia Universidad Javeriana -- GF#990-0165; 970-0838; 980-1093, 1998-2001 (Box 12)
  - Pontificia Universidad Javeriana -- GF#990-0165; 970-0838; 980-1093 -- Unitarian Universalist Service Committee (UUSC), 1998 (Box 12)
  - Social Science Research Council -- GF#990-0162 (folder 1), 1998-2000 (Box 12)
  - Social Science Research Council -- GF#990-0162 -- 2nd Workshop (folder 2), 1999 (Box 12)
  - Social Science Research Council -- GF#990-0162 -- Taller Sobre Cooperación Internacional (ACLS/SSRC), La Habana, Cuba (folder 3), May 30-31, 2000 (Box 12)
  - Social Science Research Council -- GF#990-0162 -- ACLS/SSRC Working Group on Cuba -- 8th Meeting, New York, NY (folder 4), Sep 8, 2000 (Box 12)
  - Tomas Rivera Policy Institute (The) -- GF#990-0569 (folder 1), 1998-2001 (Box 12)
  - Tomas Rivera Policy Institute (The) -- GF#990-0569 -- Extra Stuff (folder 2), 1997-1998 (Box 12)
  - Tomas Rivera Policy Institute (The) -- GF#990-0569 -- Reports incl. "Talking Back to Television" and Proposal Materials (folder 3), 1998-1999 (Box 12)
  - University of California, San Diego -- GF#980-0341, 1996 (Box 12)
  - Universidad Torcuato di Tella (UTDT/Torcuato di Tella University Foundation) -- GF#970-1805; 960-1312 -- Rut Diamint (folder 1), 1996-1997 (Box 12)
  - Universidad Torcuato di Tella (UTDT/Torcuato di Tella University Foundation) -- GF#970-1805; 960-1312 (folder 2), 1997 (Box 12)
  - Universidad Torcuato di Tella (UTDT/Torcuato di Tella University Foundation) -- GF#970-1805; 960-1312 -- South-South Connection Meeting, Argentina (folder 3), Apr 1998 (Box 12)
  - Universidad Torcuato di Tella (UTDT/Torcuato di Tella University Foundation) -- GF#970-1805; 960-1312 -- Report No. 3, "The Civil-Military Issue in Latin America" (folder 4), Oct 1999 (Box 12)
  - Universidad Torcuato di Tella (UTDT/Torcuato di Tella University Foundation) -- GF#970-1805; 960-1312 -- Planning (folder 5), 2000 (Box 12)
  - Videoteca del Sur -- GF#990-1024 -- Gloria Rolando, Humberto Solas Screenplay (folder 1), 1998-1999 (Box 12)
  - Videoteca del Sur -- GF#990-1024 (folder 2), 1998-2001 (Box 12)
  - Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars (no grant file number), 2000 (Box 13)
  - Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars (Wilson Center) -- GF#970-0972; 960-0526 (folder 1), 1995 (Box 13)
  - Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars (Wilson Center) -- GF#970-0972; 960-0526 (folder 2), 1996 (Box 13)
  - Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars (Wilson Center) -- GF#970-0972; 960-0526 -- FY 1997 (folder 3), 1996 (Box 13)
  - Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars (Wilson Center) -- GF#970-0972; 960-0526 -- Junior Scholars Program (folder 4), 1996 (Box 13)
  - Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars (Wilson Center) -- GF#970-0972; 960-0526 -- Washington, DC Conference (Mar 1997) Preparation and Related Materials (folder 5), 1996-1997 (Box 13)
  - Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars (Wilson Center) -- GF#970-0972; 960-0526 -- LACP (folder 6), 1997 (Box 13)
  - Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars (Wilson Center) -- GF#970-0972; 960-0526 (folder 7), 1998-2001 (Box 13)
- Consultant Files, 1996-2002; 5; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
  - Agrait, Nicolas, 1996-1997 (Box 13)
  - Brugger, Christian, 1997-1998 (Box 13)
  - Call, Charles T., 1998 (Box 13)
  - Diamint, Rut, 2000-2001 (Box 13)
  - Freres, Christian -- AIETI, 2002 (Box 13)
  - Gleijesus, Piero, 2000 (Box 13)
  - Lauren, Giselle, 1996 (Box 13)
  - Reed, Gail, 1998 (Box 13)
  - Rojas, Francisco, 1996 (Box 13)
  - Rolando, Gloria -- Screening, 1998 (Box 13)
  - Ruiz, Lisette, 1998 (Box 13)
  - Salas, Maria Dolores, 2001 (Box 13)
  - Whitfield, Teresa, 1997 (Box 13)
- Subject Files, 1990-2000; 6; 0.76 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes
  - International Organizations/Law (2 folders), 1990-1996 (Box 14, Folder 4-5)
    Scope and Contents
    Sections dedicated to: University of New Mexico Grant No. 9200416, Yale Grant No. 9400322, American Society of International Law, Academic Council on the United Nations System (ACUNS)/Brown University Grant No. 9200790, Pennsylvania State University Grant No. 9450951, Franklin and Eleanor Roosevelt Institute Grant No. 9550364, Rutgers University Grant No. 9001493, University of Georgia Grant No. 9001496, Columbia University Grant No. 9000864
  - Information Technology - Looking Ahead Together: International Cooperation Concept Paper (2 folders), 2000 March (Box 14, Folder 6-7)
    Prepared for The Worldwide International Cooperation Field Meeting, Santa Monica, California, Prepared by Mahnaz Ispahani
  - Central America Initiative Grantee Meeting A-I (Box 15, Folder 8)
    RGAs
  - Central America Initiative Grantee L-Z, 1995-1996 (Box 15, Folder 9)